# POOJA HARUGOP

+91 9972648029 ♦ pooja.harugop@brillio.com ♦ linkedin.com/in/pooja-harugop♦ www.github.com/poojaharugop8

### **OBJECTIVE**

Software Engineer with 1+ years of Industry Experience in Full-Stack Dev. A Hard-working, ambitious and a proactive professional to use my knowledge and skills to gain practical exposure. Being a quick learner with great Communication, Quantitative and Technical skills, I wish to develop a more rounded skill-set.

### **SKILLS**

Programming Languages: C , Java(Oracle Certified) , JavaScript
Application Development: MERN Stack, Flutter App Development

Full Stack : React , Express , Node Database : MySQL , MongoDB

Tools: VSCode, Postman, Jira, Git, GitHub

#### **EXPERIENCE**

# Brillio Technologies Full stack Developer

Health Care Project

July 2021 - Present Bangalore, IN

- Worked for a Health Care Insurance client which gained me a lot of expertise in USA's Health Structure and their requirements. Used understanding of React fundamentals to promote better component life-cycle practices, with 100% deadline adherence.
- Dedicated and efficient full stack developer with 1+ years experience in application layers, presentation layers, and databases. Certified in both F/E and B/E technologies. Seeking to further improve HTML5 and CSS3 skills as the future full stack developer at Atmospheric Solutions.
- Working as a Sergeant-at-Arms for the Brillio Toastmaster's Club. This helped me develop skills like Planning, Strong Interpersonal, Verbal and written skills.

### Campus Ambassador

March 2020 - April 2020

## National Engineering Olympiad 3.0

Belgavi, IN

NEO is an educational organization popularizing aptitude competition and assisting the development of competitive spirit among engineers in India.

### **EDUCATION**

Bachelor of Computer Science Engineer, KLS Gogte Institute of Technology Belagavi

2017 - 2021

CGPA: 9.48

- -Volunteered in Organizing Youth for Seva "Chiguru 2019" at Belagavi
- Member of Rotaract Club of KLS GIT Belagavi

### **CERTIFICATIONS**

- "Certified SAFe 5 Practitioner"
- "Oracle Certified Associate Java Programmer".
- Secured 2nd rank in Paper Presentation in the flagship festival Avalanche" organized by KLS Gogte Institute of Technology, Belagavi.